http://www.whisperingmeadows.ca/privacy-policy.html

The Whispering Meadows Privacy Policy
We will NOT rent, trade, or release your name or personal information to any third party for any reason — ever.  We hate spam as much as you do!
We have an official Privacy Policy in place, to treat your information with the respect and security that it deserves:
1. Accountability
We take full responsibility for the proper use and safekeeping of all personal information submitted to us.  We have a designated Privacy Officer who is accountable for our compliance with the following principles.  Our Privacy Officer, Randy Martin, can by contacted via our Contact page.
2. Identifying purposes
Whenever we collect your personal information, we will identify the purpose for which it will be used at or before the time the information is collected.
We collect anonymous usage statistics using tracking codes embedded in the website, to help us analyze visitor patterns and create the best possible user experience.  No personal information is gathered or stored for this purpose.
3. Consent
Your knowledge and consent are required for our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, except where inappropriate.
4. Limiting collection
Our collection of personal information is limited to that which is necessary for the purposes identified.  Information is collected only by fair and lawful means.
5. Limiting use, disclosure and retention
Your personal information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required by law.  Personal information will be retained only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
6. Accuracy
Personal information will be kept as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is necessary for the purpose for which it is used.
7. Safeguards
We will protect your personal information with security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information.
8. Openness
Specific information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information will be kept readily available.
9. Individual access
You may request infomation about the existence, use, and disclosure of your personal information, and you will be given access to that information.  You may challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate.
10. Challenging compliance
You may address a challenge concerning compliance with the above principles to our Privacy Officer, Randy Martin, via our Contact page.
<<< back to previous page
Stay in touch:
Join over 5,952 readers and sign up for our occasional emails with sales, special offers, new products, and free recipes.  Unsubscribe anytime.  Privacy guaranteed.
Copyright © 2003–2020 Whispering Meadows, Inc. • 35 Main Street South, Milverton, Ontario, Canada N0K 1M0 • 1-800-439-3081
